Guide to the Anson Phelps Stokes Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1713-1958; Series I
  - Dwight Theodore (1796-1866), Undated (Box 3, Folder 170)
    Portion of ALS (last 4 pages) to a "dear friend and classmate"
  - Dwight, Timothy (1752-1817), 1795 January 31, 1798 May 8, 1798 August 25, 1802 July 22, 1808 May 14, 1808 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    ALS to Ebenezer Huntington
    Photostat ALS to John Allen
    Photostat ALS to Jedidiah Morse
    2 ALS to Jedidiah Morse
    Typed copy letter to Jedidiah Morse
  - Dwight, Timothy (1828-1916), 1900 July 9, 1911 December 14, 1885 June 6 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    2 ALS to A. P. Stokes
    ALS to "My Dear Friend" Biographical notes
  - Dyer, Eliphalet (1721-1807), (1764 Nov) (Box 3, Folder 173)
    ALS to Maj. Elderkin
    2 ANS to A. P. Stokes from Frank Bates and Anthony Dyer re E. Dyer
  - Eames, Benjamin Tucker (1818-1901), 1872 August 9 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    ALS to Messrs. Rice and Bailey
  - Eaton, Daniel Cady (1837-1912), 1869, undated (Box 3, Folder 175)
    ALS to Noah Porter
    ALS to E. E. Salisbury [Transferred to Salisbury Family Papers]
  - Eddy, Sherwood, 1914 (April 19) (Box 3, Folder 176)
    ANS to A. P. Stokes
  - Edwards, Henry Pierrepont (1808-1855), 1853 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    ALS to Greene C. Bronson
  - Edwards, Jonathan (1703-1758), 1751 July 13 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    ALS to Rev. William Hogg; biographical notes; portrait
  - Eliot, Jared (1685-1763), Undated (Box 3, Folder 179)
    Diploma, photostats only. Original is framed.
  - Ellery, Christopher (1768-1840), 1834 July 9 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    ALS to McClintock Young
  - Elliott, John (1768-1824), 1795 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    ALS to John Woodworth
  - Elliott, John (1773-1827), 1824 July 25 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    ALS to A. L. Southard
  - Elliott, Stephen (1771-1850), 1914 April 18, 1913 May 8 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    Autograph and ms. notes (in his hand?)
    ALS to A. P. Stokes from Sarah Garnwell Elliott
    ALS to A. P. Stokes from Mabel Webber
  - Ellsworth, Henry Leavitt (1791-1858), 1834 July 30 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    ALS to F. P. Blair
  - Ellsworth, Oliver (1745-1807), 1778 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    Signed receipt for his expense account in attending Congress
  - Ellsworth, William Wolcott (1791-1868), 1830 July 17 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Ely, Ezra Stiles (1786-1861), 1836 June 27 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    ALS to William C. Anderson
  - Emmons, Nathanael (1745-1840), 1818 December 2 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    ANS recommending Willard Fisher of Franklin, Mass. as a schoolteacher; biographical notes; portrait
  - Evarts, Jeremiah (1781-1831), 1818 January 9 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    ALS to Samuel Farrar; portrait
  - Evarts, William Maxwell (1818-1901), 1865 October 11, 1863 November 28 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    ALS to President Woolsey
    ALS to Samuel Blatchford
  - Fanning, Edmund (1737-1818), 1773 October 6 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    ADS-Will of Thomas Sharp attested before Edmund Fanning; biographical notes; portrait
  - Felder, John Myers (1782-1859), 1834 May (Box 3, Folder 192)
    ALS from John Felder concerning a Naval appointment for a constituent
  - Ferry, Orris Sanford (1823-1875), 1869 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    ALS to the Collector of the Port of New York
  - Field, Rev. David Dudley (1781-1867), 1858, 1911 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    ANS-autograph of David D. Fields
    ALS to A. P. Stokes from Stephen D. Fields
    (grandson of D. D. Fields) re a likeness of
    D. D. Fields
  - Field, Maunsell Bradhurst (1822-1875), 1874 July 29 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    ALS to Charles W. Squires
  - Finch, Francis Miles (1827-1907), Undated (Box 3, Folder 196)
    Signed part of his poem "The Blue and Grey"
    biographical notes; portrait
  - Fisher, Alexander Mercalf (1794-1822), Undated, 1822 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    Notes of a religious nature, unsigned
    Eulogy delivered by James Kingsley on A. M. Fisher
  - Fisher, George Park (1827-1909), 1905 November 10 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    ALS to Rt. Hon. James Bryce
  - Fisher, Rev. Samuel Ware (1814-1874), 1862 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    ALS to L. J. Cist
  - Fitch, Rev. Ebenezer (1756-1833), 1826 May 9 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    ALS to Mason Cogswell; biographical notes
  - Fitch, Eleazar (1726-1796), 1784 March 27, April 2 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    ALS to Joshua Lathrop with note added
  - Fitch, Rev. Eleazar Thompson (1792-1872), 1866 June 11 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    ALS to Prof. E. F. Rockwell
    Print copy of a hymn by E. T. Fitch
  - Fitch, Thomas (1700-1774), 1762 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    ALS to Col. Whiting
  - Flint, Royal (1754-1797), 1780 March 10 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    ALS to Maj. G. Greene
  - Foote, Samuel Augustus (1780-1846), 1843 November 3 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    ALS to his son Lieut. A. H. Foot (sic)
  - Ford, Seabury (1802-1855), 1845 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    ALS to "Dear Friend"
  - Forward, Justus (1730-1814), 1802 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    Autographed sermon preached in 1802, unsigned
    [Transferred to Justus Forward Papers]
  - Foster, Dwight (1828-1884), 1862 July 28 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Foster, Edmund (1752-1826) (Box 3, Folder 209)
    Autographed sermon, signed, 12 pp, preached first in 1820? Dec
  - Fowler, Orin (1791-1852), Undated (Box 3, Folder 210)
    Autographed signature (Congressional letter frank)
  - Frissell, Hollis Burke (1852-1917), 1913 November 2 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    ALS to A. P Stokes
  - Gadsden, James (1788-1858), 1829 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    ALS to President Andrew Jackson; also silhouette and biographical notes
  - Gale, Dr. Benjamin (1715-1790), 1765 August 26 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    ALS to unknown recipient; also biographical notes
  - Gallaudet, Thomas Hopkins (1787-1852), 1830 January 18, 1839 October 13, 1821 may 22 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    ALS to the Pres. of Directors of the American Asylum
    ADS to the marriage of G. Waters to C. Holcombe
    Pamphlet of a discourse by T.H. Gallaudet
  - Gibbs, George (1825-1873), 1843 January 30 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    ALS to L.J. Cist; also biographical notes
  - Gibbs, Josiah Willard (1790-1861), Undated (Box 3, Folder 216)
    Signed receipt to Hezekiah Howe; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Gibbs, Josiah Willard (1839-1903), 1901 July 12, 1866 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    ALS to A.P. Stokes 2 permission slips signed to attend church elsewhere than Yale church
  - Gibson, Randall Lee (1832-1892), 1878 May 17 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    ALS to Henry Babcock; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Gillette, Francis (1807-1879), 1855 February 8 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    ALS to Mr. Barrows
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit (1831-1908), 1864 April 21 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    ALS to Samuel B. Ruggles [Transferred to Daniel Coit Gilman Papers]
    also biographical notes (2 pamphlets) and portrait
  - Gold, Thomas Ruggles (1764-1826), Undated (Box 4, Folder 221)
    ALS to Bleeker and Sedgwick
  - Goodrich, Chauncey (1759-1815), 1790 December 29, 1797 August 31 (Box 4, Folder 222)
    ALS to unknown recipient
    ALS to Stephen Jacobs Esq.
  - Goodrich, Rev. Chauncey Allen (1790-1860), Undated (Box 4, Folder 223)
    ANS to unknown recipient; also biographical notes
  - Goodrich, Elizur (1761-1849), 1779 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    ALS to Jonathan Maltbie
  - Gould, Charles Winthrop (1849-1931), 1911 November 8 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    TLS to A.P. Stokes; also biographical notes (pamphlet)
  - Gould, James (1770-1838), n.y. September 6 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    ALS to Roger Sherman Baldwin; also biog. and portrait
  - Granger, Francis (1792-1868), n.y. November 28 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    ALS to Mr. Meredith; also portrait
  - Granger, Gideon (1767-1822), 1803 August 5 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    ALS to Thomas Newton; also portrait
  - Gray, Ebenezer (1743-1795), 1777 July 31-August 19 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    Military journal from Jul 31-Aug 19, 1777 some cash accounts
  - Green, James (1841-1926), Undated (Box 4, Folder 230)
    Autographed pamphlet by James Green
    "Personal recollections of Daniel Henry Chamberlain"
  - Griffin, Edward Dorr (1770-1837), 1828 December 18 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    ALS to Rev. Dr. Richards; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Griswold, Roger (1762-1812), 1785(?) November 21 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    ALS to John McClellan
  - Griswold, Rev. Stanley (1763-1815), 1801 March 14 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    ALS to Pierpont Edwards
  - Gulliver, John Putnam (1819-1894), 1862 August 20 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    ALS to Pres. Woolsey [Transferred to Woolsey Family Papers]
  - Gurley, Rev. John (1749-1812), n.y. undated (Box 4, Folder 235)
    Autograph signature
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining (1856-1930), 1912 July 19 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    ALS to A.P. Stokes; also portrait
  - Hadley, James (1821-1872), 1869 December 25 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    ALS to Arthur Twining Hadley
  - Haldeman, Richard Jacobs (1831-1885), 1871 January 11 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    ALS to B.P. Poore
  - Hale, Nathan (1755-1776), Circa 1773-1774 (Box 4, Folder 239)
    ALS to Benjamin Tallmadge (positive photostat in verse)ca. 1773-1774
  - Hall, Rev. Lyman (1724-1790), 1783 December 20 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    TDS certificate of ownership of land by Thomas Lester
  - Hallock, Rev. Moses (1760-1837), 1829 January 8 (Box 4, Folder 241)
  - Harada, Tasuku (1863-1940), 1911 July 3 (Box 4, Folder 242)
  - Harper, William Rainey (1856-1906), 1903 July 14, n.y. October 9, 1904 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    ALS to Prof. George Goodspeed
    ANS to Prof. George Goodspeed
    TLS to Mr. Matthews; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Harris, Samuel (1814-1899), 1871 June 29 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    ANS in reference to William F. Sandford
  - Harris, William Torrey (1835-1909), 1884 August 8, 1909 March (Box 4, Folder 245)
    ANS to the publisher of The Index
    TLS to Col. William Plumb Bacon; also portrait and biographical notes
  - Harrison, Francis Burton (1873-), 1913 August 24 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    TLS to A.P. Stokes with autographed postscript
  - Harrison, Henry Baldwin (1821-1901), 1877 July 6 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    ALS to D.B. Canfield & Co.
  - Hart, Rev. Levi (1738-1808), 1796 October 5 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    ALS to William Woolworth
  - Hatoyama, Kazuo (1856-1911), Undated (Box 4, Folder 249)
    Biographical note only
  - Hawley, Joseph (1723-1788), 1770 May 25, 1757 August 1 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    2 depositions made by Aaron Lyman before Joseph Hawley in his hand
  - Hillhouse, James (1754-1832), 1778 August 29 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    ALS to Thomas Darling
  - Hillhouse, James Abraham (1789-1841), Undated, 1836 May 4, 1838 November 7 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    Fragment of verse
    ALS to Messrs. Buel & Wilson
    Autographed poem "Absolom" signed; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Hinman, Royal Ralph (1785-1868), 1842 June 9 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    TDS (with the seal of Secretary of State attached) Conn. Gen. Assembly Resolution passed
  - Hitchcock, Edward (1793-1864), 1836 December 2 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    ALS to an unidentified recipient; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Hitchcock, Rev. Henry Lawrence (1813-1873), 1842 September 9 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    ALS to Peter Hitchcock (father); also portrait
  - Hitchcock, Peter (1781-1854), 1812 December 23, 1846 November 18 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    ALS to Thomas Worthington
    ALS to Mrs. Peter Hitchcock; also portrait
  - Hitchcock, Samuel Johnson (1786-1845), 1825 September 13 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    Resolution of Phi Beta Kappa
    signed by Samuel J. Hitchcock to thank James G. Percival
  - Hobart, John Sloss (1738-1805), 1787 June 8 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    ADS giving Col. Aaron Burr power of attorney for Robert Ely, sworn before John S. Hobart
  - Holley, Horace (1781-1827), 1822 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    ALS to Martin Rutter
  - Holmes, Rev. Abiel (1763-1837), 1822 June 10 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    ALS to Samuel Farrar; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Holt, Thomas (1762-1836), 1785 August 20 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    ALS to Jonathan Maltby
  - Hooker, John (1729-1777), 1753 August 19, 28 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    Handwritten sermon on Psalm CX.3 preached
  - Hopkins, Rev. Samuel (1729-1803), Undated 1746 January 30, 1799 October 14 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    MS. Sermon (20 pages)
    MS. Sermon on Jer. 17.9.10
    ALS to Rev. Levi Hart; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Hopkins, Samuel Miles (1772-1837), 1819 November 22 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    ALS to Smith Thompson
  - Hoppin, William Jones (1813-1895), 1864 December 19 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    ALS to S.B. Ruggles
  - Hoppin, William Warner (1807-1890), 1855 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 266)
    ALS to E.T. Creeson
  - Hosmer, Stephen Titus (1763-1834), 1789 April 30 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    ADS certifying the sale of a negro by Le Meilleur de Bellarive
  - Hosmer, Titus (1737-1780), 1773 April 2 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    Docket Hartford County
  - Hotchkiss, John (1731-1779), 1763 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    TDS Deed conveying land from John
    Hotchkiss to Nathan Beers
  - Hoyt, Henry Martyn (1861-1927), 1896 November 30 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    ALS to Dr. Charles E. Rice
  - Hubbard, Rev. Bela (1739-1812), 1783 November 30, 1784 July 3 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    MS. Sermon on Proverbs 4.23
    MS. bill of exchange payable to Isaac Beers
  - Hubbard, Rev. John (1727-1786), Undated (Box 4, Folder 272)
    MS. Sermon on Galatians 2.16-17; also biographical note
  - Hubbard, Joseph Stillman (1823-1863), Undated (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Hubbard, Oliver Payson (1809-1900), 1889 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    ALS to B.W. Austin
  - Hubbard, Samuel (1785-1847), 1817 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    ALS to Thomas Aspinwall
  - Hubbard, Samuel Dickinson (1799-1855), 1848 January 4 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    Petition to the President signed by 5 politicians including S.D. Hubbard re: Josiah Tatnall appointment
  - Hubbard, Thomas Hill (1780-1857), 1810 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    ALS to Messrs. Jonathan and E. Little and John Breath
  - Hull, Gen. William (1753-1825), 1778 May 18, 1799 March 7 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    ALS to Andrew Adams
    ALS to Silas Hathaway; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Hume, Edward Hicks (1876-), 1912 November 18 (Box 5, Folder 279)
  - Hume, Robert Allen (1847-1928), 1870 July 15 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    ALS a recommendation of Edward R. Dunham
  - Humphrey, Rev. Herman (1779-1861), 1840 November 25 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    ALS to L.J. Cist
  - Humphreys, David (1752-1818), 1782 September 24, 1785 February 10, 1796 December 10 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    ALS Gen. Nathanael Greene
    ALS (neg. photostat) to Monsieur Dumas
    ALE to Rufus King
  - Humphreys, Rev. Hector (1797-1857), Undated, 1862 March 5 (Box 5, Folder 283)
    ALS (fragment) to his son
    ALS from M. Humphreys (H. Humphreys' wife) to A.P. Stokes
  - Hungerford, William (-1873 Y. 1809) (Box 5, Folder 284)
    note by A.P. Stokes stating that no Hungerford item had been found
  - Hunt, Thomas Sterry (1826-1892), 1861 September 30 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    ALS to Prof. Benjamin Silliman Jr. [Transferred to Silliman Family Papers]
  - Huntington, Benjamin (1736-1800), 1777 May 3 (date of endorsement) (Box 5, Folder 286)
    ADS order to The Committee of Pay Table for 15000 pounds in favor of E. Ledyard
  - Huntington, Gen. Ebenezer (1754-1834), 1827 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    ALS to Ephraim Bateman
  - Huntington, Jabez (1719-1786), 1772 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    Printed documents signed Deed transferring land to Samuel Huntington
  - Huntington, Jabez Williams (1788-1847), n.y. December 15 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    ALS to Levi Woodbury
  - Huntington, Rev. Joseph (1735-1794), 1783 January 25 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    ALS to his son Samuel
  - Huntington, Samuel (1765-1817), 1795 April 24, 1815 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 291)
    Printed document signed: Bond given for the sum of $2,000.00
    Ms. List of taxable property signed
  - Hurd, John Codman (1816-1892), 1864 March 18 (Box 5, Folder 292)
    ALS to Dr. Francis Lieber
  - Ingersoll, Charles Anthony (1798-1860), 1858 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 293)
    ALS to N.K. Hall
  - Ingersoll, Charles Robert (1821-1903), Undated (Box 5, Folder 294)
    ALS to T.A. Cheney; also portrait
  - Ingersoll, Jared (1722-1781), 1760 April 18 (endorsed) (Box 5, Folder 295)
    Order to pay Jared Ingersoll 100 pounds from Gr. Brit. Exchequer
  - Ingersoll, Jared (1749-1822), 1809 January 3 (Box 5, Folder 296)
    ALS to Elias Boudinot
  - Ingersoll, Jonathan (1747-1823), 1814 August 16 (Box 5, Folder 297)
    ALS to Andrew Kingsbury
  - Ingersoll, Ralph Isaacs (1788-1872), 1827 October 24 (Box 5, Folder 298)
    ALS to S.L. Southard
  - Jackson, Henry Rootes (1820-1898), 1866 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 299)
    ALS to Gov. Charles Jenkins
  - Jacob, Stephen (1755-1817), 1788 February 6 (Box 5, Folder 300)
    ALS to Goldsbrow Banyar
  - Jay, William (1789-1858), 1842 April 7 (Box 5, Folder 301)
    ALS to J.J. Roosevelt
  - Jessup, William (1797-1868), 1845 November 6 (Box 5, Folder 302)
    ALS to Harrison Wright
  - Johnson, Alexander Smith (1817-1878), 1855 November 28 (Box 5, Folder 303)
    ALS to John C Rives; also biographical notes and picture
  - Johnson, Owen McMahon (1878-1952), 1910 December 13, n.y. November 11 (Box 5, Folder 304)
    ALS (neg. photostat) to Mr. Stokes
  - Johnson, Rev. Samuel (1696-1772), 1741 December 21 (Box 5, Folder 305)
    ALS to William Samuel Johnson; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Johnson, Samuel William (1830-1909), 1860 October 10 (Box 5, Folder 306)
    ALS to Joseph E. Sheffield; also portrait and biographical notes
  - Johnson, Rev. Stephen (1724-1786), 1766 April 4 (Box 5, Folder 307)
  - Johnson, William (1770-1848), 1816 November 4 (Box 5, Folder 308)
    ALS to T.H. Hubbard
  - Johnson, William Samuel (1727-1819), 1754 May 16, 1775 December 15, 1787 May 30 (Box 5, Folder 309)
    ALS to "Sir"
    TDS summons for Bela Strong to appear in court
    ALS to his son
  - Johnston, Henry Phelps (1842-1923), 1909 April 24 (Box 5, Folder 310)
  - Johnston, William Preston (1831-1899), 1875 November 8 (Box 5, Folder 311)
    ALS to Thomas Reynolds; also biographical notes
  - Jones, Timothy (1737-1800), 1763 February 16, 1763 February 17 (Box 5, Folder 312)
    ADS: deed from J. Mix. to Nathan Beers
    Witnessed by T. Jones
  - Judd, Rev. Jonathan (1720-1803), 1788 July 30 (Box 5, Folder 313)
    Autograph
  - Judd, Sylvester (1813-1853), Undated (Box 5, Folder 314)
    Fragment of ALS to unidentified recipient
  - Judson, David (1755-1818), 1780 December 5 (Box 5, Folder 315)
    Autograph memorandum
  - Kane, John Kintzing (1795-1858), 1848 January 10 (Box 5, Folder 316)
    ALS to William Mathiot
  - Kellogg, Martin (1828-1903), 1901 November 14, 1902 March 1 (Box 5, Folder 317)
    2 ALS to E.L. Parsons
  - Kellogg, Stephen Wright (1822-1904), 1870 January 25 (Box 5, Folder 318)
  - Kent, James (1763-1847), 1834 September 7 (Box 5, Folder 319)
    ALS to George Bancroft; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Kimberly, Dennis (1790-1862), 1862 June 13 (Box 5, Folder 320)
    ANS to Nathan Smith
  - King, Clarence (1842-1901), 1869(?) November 2 (Box 5, Folder 321)
    ALS to Prof. George Brush; also biographical notes and portrait
  - Kingsley, James Luce (1778-1852), 1850 April 1 (Box 5, Folder 322)
    Autograph with quote from Cicero (in Latin)
  - Kinne, Rev. Aaron (1745-1824), Undated (Box 5, Folder 323)
    Autograph signature; also biographical notes
  - Kip, Rt. Rev. William Ingraham (1811-1893), 1869 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 324)
    ALS to Rev. Dr. Ballard
  - Kirtland, Jared Potter (1793-1877), 1826 (Box 5, Folder 325)
    Autograph signature MS. page from medical lectures and signature
  - Lang, Henry Roseman (1858-1934), 1907 November 23 (Box 5, Folder 326)
  - Langdon, Chauncey (1763-1830), 1810 January 20 (Box 5, Folder 327)
    ALS to Jonathan Little
  - Lanman, James (1767-1841), 1790 August 24, 1823 December 2 (Box 5, Folder 328)
    Samuel Southard
  - Lathrop, John Hiram (1799-1866) A, 1827 December 15 (Box 5, Folder 329)
    ALS to Gerrit Smith
  - Lathrop, Joseph (1731-1820), 1764 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 330)
    MS. Sermon on John III 2.5 preached at West Springfield
  - Lathrop, Samuel (1772-1846), 1827 January 29 (Box 5, Folder 331)
  - Law, John (1796-1873), 1841 January 12 (Box 5, Folder 332)
    ALS to F. Thomas
  - Law, Richard (1733-1806), 1788 July 11 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    ADS: Writ of Attachment between Thomas Lewis and Henry Totten and George and Robert Lewis
  - Learned, Dwight Whitney (1848-1943), 1911 August 23 (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - Leavenworth, Elias Warner (1803-1887), 1857 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    ALS to John W Swift; also portrait
  - Leavenworth, Jesse (1740-1826), 1769 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    TDS: deed transferring land to Nathan Beers
  - Leavenworth, Rev. Mark (1712?-1797), 1760 June 18 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    ALS to his wife Sarah
  - Leavitt, Rev. Joshua (1794-1873), Undated1864 June 30 (Box 5, Folder 338)
    ALS to S.B. Ruggles; also biographical notes
  - Lee Rev. Andrew (1745-1832), 1794 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 339)
    ALS to Joseph Dana
  - Lee, Rev. Chauncey (1763-1842), 1836 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    MS. Sermon on Isaiah 41.27 preached
  - L'Hommedieu, Ezra (1734-1811), Undated (Box 5, Folder 341)
    ADS certifying bond given by Daniel Osborn
  - Lines, Edwin Stevens (1845-1927), 1908 October 20 (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - Livingston, John Henry (1746-1825), 1808 February 25 (Box 5, Folder 343)
    ALS to Rev. Charles Lowell
  - Livingston, Philip (1716-1778), 1754 November 6 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    ADS addressed to the sheriff of New York, signed by Livingston and others; biographical notes; portrait
  - Livingston, William (1723-1790), 1782 April 26, 1779 October 13 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    ALS to William Moore
    TDS Marriage license for P. Sample and Martha Severno
  - Lockwood, Rev. Samuel (1721-1791), 1787 December (Box 5, Folder 346)
    Ms. Sermon on Mark 4:24; biographical note
  - Lockwood, Rev. William (1753-1828), 1787 September 29 (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - Loomis, Elias (1811-1889), 1886 May 6 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    ALS to unidentified recipient; biographical notes; portrait
  - Longstreet, Augustus Baldwin (1790-1870), 1855 October 27 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    ALS to Bishop John L. Spalding; biographical notes; portrait
  - Lord, Frederick William (1801?-1860), 1849 February 24 (Box 5, Folder 350)
    ALS to John Towers
  - Lounsbury, Thomas Raynesford (1838-1915), 1914 December 11, 18(?)July 20 (Box 6, Folder 351)
    ANS re Wellington Campbell
  - Lovett, John (1761-1818), 1786 January 24, 1786 March 17 (Box 6, Folder 352)
  - Lowell, Abbott Lawrence (1856-1943), 1911 March 22 (Box 6, Folder 353)
    Typed copy of a letter to Max Farrand
  - Lusk, William Thompson (1838-1877), Undated (Box 6, Folder 354)
    Last page of ALS to unknown correspondent
  - Lyman, Hart (1851-1927), 1913 March 27 (Box 6, Folder 355)
  - Lyman, Phineas (1716-1774), Undated, Undated (Box 6, Folder 356)
    ANS to Col. Thomas Seymour
    Lithograph of Battle of Lake George; biographical notes
  - Lynde, William Pitt (1817-1885), 1866 January 11 (Box 6, Folder 357)
    ALS to the publishers of the Daily Globe
  - McClure, Rev. David (1748-1820), 1781 October 26 (Box 6, Folder 358)
    ALS to John. Wheelock
  - McCurdy, Charles Johnson (1797-1891), 1854 May 4 (Box 6, Folder 359)
    ALS to L. F. S. Foster
  - McKinstry, John (1723-1813), 1770 December (Box 6, Folder 360)
    Ms. Sermon on I Chronicles 16:29; biographical notes
  - McLaughlin, Edward Thompkins (1860-1893), Undated (Box 6, Folder 361)
    Poem, typed and untitled
  - MacVeagh, Wayne (1833-1917), 1870 June 2 (Box 6, Folder 362)
    ALS to Gen. Bedeau (?)